aizaku.com 2009-12-23

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Aizaku uses and protects any information that you give Aizaku when you use this website and all other Aizaku websites.

Aizaku is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website or any other Aizaku website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  

Aizaku may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 6/1/2009.

We may collect the following information:  

Name  

Contact information including email address  

Demographic information such as preferences and interests  

Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers  

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe option at the bottom of the email you recieved.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
